(Tan Group.)
(مجموعة تان.)
(Eight years ago, you brought my family to ruin.)
(قبل ثماني سنوات، تسببت في خراب عائلتي.)
(Are you ready to settle the score?)
(هل أنت مستعد لتصفية الحسابات؟)
Father.
أب.
(From this moment on,)
(من هذه اللحظة فصاعدًا،)
(everything here)
(كل شيء هنا)
(belongs to the Tan Group.)
(ينتمي إلى مجموعة تان.)
From today onward,
ابتداءً من اليوم فصاعداً،
you are nothing more than an outcast.
أنت لست سوى منبوذ.
An outcast,
منبوذ،
left to survive on scraps.
تُرك ليعيش على الفتات.
Mr. Tan.
السيد تان.
It is time to collect the interest.
حان وقت تحصيل الفائدة.
=Secret By My Name=
=سر باسمي=
(Adapted from the novel Hotpot Loves Tangyuan by Ye Yijian)
(مقتبس من رواية "هوت بوت يعشق تانغ يوان" للكاتبة يي ييجيان)
=Episode 1=
=الحلقة 1=
This suit is our department's latest design.
هذا الزي هو أحدث تصميم لقسمنا .
It uses the most popular striped elements of the moment.
يستخدم هذا التصميم أكثر العناصر المخططة رواجاً في الوقت الحالي.
A design this drawn out,
تصميم بهذا الطول،
are you trying to make the Tan Group a laughingstock?
هل تحاول أن تجعل مجموعة تان أضحوكة؟
Do not try to brush me off with this kind of work again.
لا تحاول أن تتجاهلني بهذا النوع من العمل مرة أخرى.
Or you can leave the Tan Group.
أو يمكنك مغادرة مجموعة تان.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
Speak.
يتكلم.
Did you understand?
هل فهمت؟
I understand.
أفهم.
Fei.
فاي.
Do not be anxious.
لا تقلق.
Design work like this
تصميمات كهذه
needs time to be refined.
يحتاج إلى وقت لتحسينه.
You know that.
أنت تعلم ذلك.
Change the peak lapel to a lightweight double breasted lapel.
استبدل طية صدر السترة المدببة بطية صدر مزدوجة خفيفة الوزن.
Raise the waistline by two centimeters.
ارفعي خط الخصر بمقدار سنتيمترين.
Replace the gold plated buttons with obsidian buttons.
استبدل الأزرار المطلية بالذهب بأزرار من حجر الأوبسيديان.
As for this moldy lining,
أما بالنسبة لهذه البطانة المتعفنة،
if President Wang tries it on himself, it would actually suit him quite well.
إذا جربه الرئيس وانغ على نفسه، فسوف يناسبه ذلك تماماً.
So it was you.
إذن أنت كنت أنت.
Miss Li, eight years ago,
الآنسة لي، قبل ثماني سنوات،
you were driven out in disgrace.
لقد طُردت في خزي وعار.
And now you still have the nerve
والآن ما زلت تملك الجرأة
to come back and show your face.
أن تعود وتظهر وجهك.
Mr. Wang, your memory seems rather poor.
سيد وانغ، يبدو أن ذاكرتك ضعيفة نوعاً ما.
When you were overseas last week
عندما كنت في الخارج الأسبوع الماضي
and lost two rosewood production lines,
وخسرت خطي إنتاج خشب الورد،
the way you knelt and begged your creditors for mercy
الطريقة التي ركعت بها وتوسلت إلى دائنيك طلباً للرحمة
was far more sincere than anything you show now.
كان ذلك أكثر صدقاً بكثير من أي شيء تُظهره الآن.
You swore you would repay everything within one month.
أقسمت أنك ستسدد كل شيء في غضون شهر واحد.
Make a sound like a dog,
أصدر صوتاً يشبه صوت الكلب،
and I will let you leave today.
وسأسمح لك بالمغادرة اليوم.
Woof.
نباح.
Woof, woof.
نباح، نباح.
You... Give that back to me.
أنت... أعد ذلك إليّ.
Mr. Wang is now perfectly suited to endorse Tan Group's new product line.
السيد وانغ الآن هو الشخص المناسب تماماً للترويج لخط إنتاج مجموعة تان الجديد.
After all, the theme of predatory capital
في النهاية، موضوع رأس المال المفترس
is something you portray effortlessly.
إنه شيء تُجسّده بسهولة.
Security.
حماية.
Someone come here.
ليأتِ أحدٌ إلى هنا.
Get this woman out of here.
أخرجوا هذه المرأة من هنا.
Get out.
اخرج.
You should never have come back.
كان يجب ألا تعود أبداً.
I came back this time to take a few things.
عدت هذه المرة لأخذ بعض الأشياء.
Your power.
قوتك.
His life.
حياته.
And also,
وأيضًا،
the thing you hold every night when you sleep.
الشيء الذي تمسكه كل ليلة وأنت نائم.
My old school uniform.
زي مدرستي القديم.
(Tan Group)
(مجموعة تان)
I am very pleased to work with all of you to create a brilliant future together.
يسعدني جداً العمل معكم جميعاً لخلق مستقبل مشرق معاً.
I appreciate your support.
أقدر دعمكم.
Li Shujing.
لي شوجينغ.
You went to great lengths to stage all of this.
لقد بذلت جهوداً كبيرة لتدبير كل هذا.
Did you really think
هل كنت تعتقد حقاً
this would get you into the Tan Group?
هل هذا سيؤهلك للانضمام إلى مجموعة تان؟
Li Shujing's consulting agreement
اتفاقية الاستشارة الخاصة بـ Li Shujing
was signed
تم التوقيع
by me personally.
من قبلي شخصياً.
Mr. Tan disappeared for two years, and has finally reappeared.
اختفى السيد تان لمدة عامين، ثم عاد للظهور أخيراً.
An agreement signed by the dead
اتفاقية موقعة من قبل الموتى
is overruled by rules set by the living.
يتم تجاوزها بقواعد وضعها الأحياء.
From today onward,
ابتداءً من اليوم فصاعداً،
every single stitch of the Autumn Winter Alpine Collection
كل غرزة من مجموعة الخريف والشتاء الألبية
will follow my rules.
سوف يلتزم بقواعدي.
We are not going home yet.
لن نعود إلى المنزل بعد.
We are going somewhere else.
سنذهب إلى مكان آخر.
Eight years.
ثماني سنوات.
And all you learned was how to burn discarded drafts.
وكل ما تعلمته هو كيفية حرق المسودات المهملة.
When you bit through my collarbone back then,
عندما عضضت عظمة الترقوة خاصتي آنذاك،
you were far more ruthless than you are now.
كنتَ أكثر قسوة بكثير مما أنت عليه الآن.
I am designing funeral invitations for the Tan Group.
أقوم بتصميم دعوات جنازة لمجموعة تان.
The main image
الصورة الرئيسية
should be the bite mark on your collarbone. What do you think?
يفترض أن تكون علامة العضة على عظمة الترقوة. ما رأيك؟
After all, this is the Tan Group's
في النهاية، هذا هو مشروع مجموعة تان
only thing that was ever real.
الشيء الوحيد الذي كان حقيقياً على الإطلاق.
Instead of burning these useless drafts,
بدلاً من حرق هذه المسودات عديمة الفائدة،
you might as well burn me.
يمكنك حرقي.
That was your plan eight years ago anyway.
كانت تلك خطتك قبل ثماني سنوات على أي حال.
Back then, you were a truant teenager.
في ذلك الوقت، كنت مراهقاً متغيباً عن المدرسة.
Now, you are the president of the Tan Group.
أنت الآن رئيس مجموعة تان.
It does make me feel
هذا يجعلني أشعر
more accomplished than before.
أكثر إنجازاً من ذي قبل.
Then this time, remember to change the knot.
ثم تذكر هذه المرة أن تغير العقدة.
The bow you tied back then
القوس الذي ربطته حينها
was far too easy to break free from.
كان من السهل جداً التحرر منه.
Li Shujing.
لي شوجينغ.
Every sheet of paper you burn here proves that you still cannot forget
كل ورقة تحرقها هنا تثبت أنك ما زلت لا تستطيع النسيان
the fool who willingly let you
الأحمق الذي سمح لك بذلك عن طيب خاطر
tie him up back then.
اربطه حينها.
But let me make this clear.
لكن دعني أوضح هذا الأمر.
The Tan Group today
مجموعة تان اليوم
has no room for two living corpses in its coffin.
لا يوجد مكان لجثتين على قيد الحياة في نعشها.
You do not seriously think that in these eight years
أنت لا تعتقد بجدية أنه خلال هذه السنوات الثماني
all I learned was how to mourn, do you?
كل ما تعلمته هو كيفية الحداد، هل تعلم أنت ذلك؟
Look closely.
انظر جيداً.
I carved my own tombstone long ago
لقد نحتت شاهد قبري بنفسي منذ زمن بعيد
into climbing pitons.
في أوتاد التسلق.
So tell me,
أخبرني إذن،
from which floor of the Tan Group
من أي طابق في مجموعة تان
will the sound of bones and lies
هل سيظل صوت العظام والأكاذيب
shattering together be loud enough to hear?
هل سيكون صوت تحطمهما معًا عاليًا بما يكفي لسماعه؟
Then take your pitons
ثم خذ أوتادك
and move into the top floor.
والانتقال إلى الطابق العلوي.
After all, the teeth that once bit through my collarbone
في النهاية، الأسنان التي كانت تعض عظمة الترقوة الخاصة بي
were never meant to belong to a well behaved girl.
لم يكن من المفترض أن تنتمي إلى فتاة حسنة السلوك.
♪A lone bird flying against the crowd♪
♪طائر وحيد يحلق عكس اتجاه الحشد♪
♪Shaking off the dust, yet still circling back♪
♪ينفض الغبار، لكنه لا يزال يعود أدراجه♪
♪Following time's hidden veins toward the next dawn♪
♪نتبع عروق الزمن الخفية نحو الفجر التالي♪
♪Besieged by the night sealed deep below♪
♪محاصرون بالليل، مختومون في الأعماق♪
♪As the mist clears, searching for light's cure♪
♪مع انقشاع الضباب، بحثًا عن علاج النور♪
♪The road is narrow, yet the way I came is not forgotten♪
♪الطريق ضيق، لكن الطريق الذي أتيت منه لم يُنسَ♪
♪An ending that can never be undone♪
♪نهاية لا يمكن التراجع عنها♪
♪Disrupting the old rhythm, laying traps♪
♪إفساد الإيقاع القديم، ونصب الفخاخ♪
♪A board full of snares♪
♪لوح مليء بالطبول♪
♪Carving the past into every smile and word♪
♪ننقش الماضي في كل ابتسامة وكلمة♪
♪After falling, still searching for♪
♪بعد السقوط، ما زلت أبحث♪
♪The old marks♪
♪العلامات القديمة♪
♪Pages filled with attempts to hide the past♪
♪صفحات مليئة بمحاولات إخفاء الماضي♪
♪The next page♪
♪الصفحة التالية♪
♪Is turned, revealing this land of right and wrong♪
♪تتحول، كاشفةً عن هذه الأرض التي فيها الحق والباطل♪
♪A lone bird flying against the crowd♪
♪طائر وحيد يحلق عكس اتجاه الحشد♪
♪Shaking off the dust, yet still circling back♪
♪ينفض الغبار، لكنه لا يزال يعود أدراجه♪
♪Following time's hidden veins toward the next dawn♪
♪نتبع عروق الزمن الخفية نحو الفجر التالي♪
♪Besieged by the night sealed deep below♪
♪محاصرون بالليل، مختومون في الأعماق♪
♪As the mist clears, searching for light's cure♪
♪مع انقشاع الضباب، بحثًا عن علاج النور♪
♪The road is narrow, yet the way I came is not forgotten♪
♪الطريق ضيق، لكن الطريق الذي أتيت منه لم يُنسَ♪
♪The way I came♪
♪الطريقة التي أتيت بها♪